[Meet Yourself]
[Episode 25]
What are you looking at?
Why are you laughing so happily?
Am I disturbing you?
No. Not at all.
I've finished writing it.
Just check again.
Why aren't Hongdou and Hu back yet?
The singer in the town bar has left,
so Hu went to the bar for an audition today
Hongdou should be
playing mahjong at Mr. Xie's.
Granny Xie has recently become
addicted to playing mahjong.
This progress bar is too slow.
What progress bar?
The progress bar of love.
There is no progress bar of
love between the two of them.
Hongdou has been here too short,
only two or three months.
When she leaves,
they'll be going their separate ways.
There won't be romance
between them at all.
No.
I don't think it has
anything to do with time.
You know This is not
where her career is headed.
Marriage nowadays is not like in old times
when where the needle goes, the thread follows.
A girl has to consider
the whole picture.
That's right.
Career first.
Exactly.
Career comes first.
When you have your career,
then you can start to pursue other things.
You're right.
But Huang,
you've come here to work
on your business for so long.
Why don't you find a boyfriend here, though?
I have a boyfriend.
He is a teacher in Guizhou Province.
We were just together last month.
Why do you have the time
to find a boyfriend in Guizhou?
Last summer I went to
Guizhou to visit my parents.
My mom told me before I
went to Guizhou that they had
a new volunteer teacher
which was definitely my type.
They were effusive
in their praise for him.
When I arrived,
I saw him in person.
The young man is indeed a gentleman
who always speaks tenderly
and has a dependable disposition.
Most importantly,
he'll be shy if you look straight at him.
And his face turns flushed.
My mom knows my
preference so well.
I can't believe your mom introduced him to you.
I also have a good impression
of him so we keep in touch.
And we decided to confess
our love for each other,
and become a couple.
So you two are having a
long-distance online relationship.
But now I have an idea
that I want to poach
him here from my mom.
Our school is also short of teachers.
Is he willing to do so?
He...
He is reluctant for the moment.
Let your mom talk to him.
My mom is even more reluctant.
My mom told me
that the students
he is teaching now are about to
take the senior high school
entrance examination,
and told me not to even think about it.
All members of your family are so funny.
Just my mom.
Qin is running a grocery store
which hasn't got much business.
I guess her business
won't last long.
Besides, the boy she likes,
doesn't have a decent job.
Her parents must
be worried about her.
There's no use being worried.
Parents can't make the decision
for their children.
Qin's dad asked about
Xiaxia the other day.
Why did he ask about Xiaxia?
He's satisfied with Xiaxia,
thinking that he has good skills.
Is he truly satisfied with Xiaxia?
He thought our family was poor two years ago.
That was two years ago.
Now is different.
Xiaxia has learned the craft,
and we all know him well.
Right?
Then if there is a good girl,
we must introduce her to Xiaxia at once.
Xiaxia is still young.
We should consider Yao first.
We don't need to worry about Yao
since Xiaochun is making efforts.
I heard that Xiaochun
knew a female owner
of a restaurant in town
who looks beautiful.
Is she going to introduce that girl to Yao?
Aunt Gui, don't just chat.
Play mahjong.
Three characters.
Xiaochun talked about it at home.
Yao, what do you think?
No.
I already told her not to do this,
and focus on her job.
Is going to meet that girl a problem?
That's not what I meant.
Can this Xiaochun
put her mind on work?
She is so busy with her work all day long.
Why does she have the time
to think about trivial things.
This is an important matter.
Right?
Exactly.
Auntie,
you need to reason with him.
If you wanna reason with him,
just do it yourself.
I can't do it.
He has informed me
to understand the situation
and give up illusions.
What is "to understand the
situation and give up illusions"?
Why did you kick me?
I... I have long legs.
Don't look at my tiles.
We're like a bunch of
back-seat drivers, giving unwanted advice.
But Yao didn't even care about it.
Hongdou,
what do you think about Yao?
He's nice.
I'm asking if he's your type.
No.
Why?
I prefer a lighter skin tone.
Don't peek at my tiles.
I didn't.
Xiaochun, we're here.
Hongdou.
You...
Why are you here?
Didn't you ask Hongdou for dinner?
I happened to be in the neighborhood
so I came to eat together.
What's wrong?
Is there anything that you're gonna tell her
but can't be known by me?
Well,
we're having a girls' talk.
Don't be a meddler.
Go back to the store.
Let Nana make a
potato pancake for you.
Are you really gona shoo me away?
Xiaochun,
Why are you standing at the door?
I'm coming.
Hurry.
Well,
come with us if you want.
Let's go, Hongdou.
What?
Let's go.
Xie Xiaochun, mind your attitude!
Let me introduce her to you.
This is the owner of the store.
Wei, this is a good friend of mine,
Xu Hongdou.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
This is my brother, Xie Zhiyao.
Glad to meet you.
Mr. Xie,
you have time to
come over today?
Yes.
He's free today.
Then let's go sit in the yard
so that it's more convenient to chat.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go, Hongdou.
Feel free to order.
Be my guest.
Lunch is on me today.
I've been talking about
inviting Xiaochun to dinner.
But she's been busy.
I can't let you pay
for this meal today.
Hongdou has been here for so long
and she will soon be leaving,
but I haven't even treated her once.
So I should pay for the meal.
Hongdou doesn't work here?
No, I don't.
I'm here for a vacation in Mr. Xie's yard.
I'm a tenant.
So this is a farewell meal today?
Is it appropriate for me to stay here?
Yes. It's totally fine.
Just a meal. Don't worry.
Then I'll buy you all a drink.
I have a nice bottle of red wine here.
Let's open it today.
I'll go get it.
No, no!
Wei, you don't have to!
She is such a born socializer, isn't she?
Hey, brother
did you not remember
anything I said to you before?
What?
Didn't I tell you about Sun Xiaowei,
the owner of Fusion Cuisine Restaurant?
And I planned to introduce her to you.
He refused.
But I couldn't tell her like that.
I told her that you
didn't have the time.
When you're free you will definitely come.
Why are you looking at me?
I didn't ask you to come.
You asked to come yourself.
Then, I'll leave.
Why are you leaving now?
I let you go just now,
but you didn't.
Are we ready to order?
Well, I'll get a burger and a salami pancake,
okay?
- What about you, Hongdou?
- A chicken burrito.
Sure.
I...
I'm okay with anything.
Okay.
Please wait a moment. I'll inform the kitchen.
Cheers!
What a happy day.
Indeed.
Earlier Xiaochun said that
Mr. Xie hasn't got the time.
I was thinking about
going to Mr. Xie's stable to ride a horse.
But my place was
just open so I didn't go.
We're all busy.
If you ask our neighbors about Mr. Xie,
they all know that
he is a successful
businessman and a good-looking
and warm-hearted person.
I'm so flattered.
Don't listen to their nonsense.
This is not nonsense.
You're indeed handsome
as far as I'm concerned.
But,
How come you don't have a girlfriend?
Well,
my brother is an unrecognized eligible bachelor
who has been devoted to his career.
Unrecognized eligible bachelor.
I thought so too at first.
Later,
I found out that he was actually not.
He's got a high standard of choosing a spouse.
He's patient with finding the best match,
unlike some other men
who has a wife but
still looks for mistresses.
He's not like that.
I'm not that noble.
It's just that nobody likes me.
Let's not talk about it.
Come on.
Bottoms up!
Come on!
Cheers!
Bottoms up?
Bottoms up!
Why didn't you say something for me?
I've said everything for you.
All I said about you was compliments.
I said you're righteous
and filial.
Are you helping me or are
you helping me find a match?
Wei thought you were
here for a blind date.
But you shouldn't go along with what she said.
I tried my best to get away
with the blind-date topic
but you just brought it back again.
Well,
what Wei asked is not a big deal.
But since she asked me,
I had to answer.
Great.
Now she thought
I was so eager to be on a blind date with her,
and I found myself
two silver-tongued helpers with me.
What Xiaochun did is enough.
And you!
Do you want me to find a date so badly?
Do you?
No.
That's not what I meant.
Why is Xiaochun so slow?
I still have something to do.
I can't wait any longer. Gotta go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hongdou.
Where's Yao?
He's left for work.
Why did he leave so soon?
I'm so sorry.
I thought the ambiance of this restaurant
is quite good
so I brought you here.
I didn't expect...
The dishes are great.
Where are you going?
I'm going back to the warehouse.
And you?
I'll go to visit Granny Xie.
Then let's go together.
Have you eaten?
Yes.
And I feel sleepy.
Come.
Sit here.
What's the sigh?
What's bothering you?
My mind is a little bit confused.
You've thought too much.
The more you think about it,
the more troublesome it is.
Granny,
I wonder why a
person can't be exactly
what you want them to be?
Why can't you have all you want in him?
You can't be so greedy.
When you have a thousand bucks,
you want ten thousand.
When you become an emperor,
you want to be god.
A man only has two hands.
No matter how much fortune is in front of you,
you only have two hands to hold them.
If you take a gold bracelet
and a silver bracelet,
you won't be able to take a jade bracelet.
How can you have
anything you want?
We can't have everything we want.
I got it.
When will you leave?
In a few days.
Then come here for
meal a few more times.
I'd love to.
Granny,
I think
you smell like my grandma.
What do I smell like?
The smell of baking bread.
That's the smell of burning firewood.
Granny,
you must stay healthy!
You need to listen to Yao.
Remember to go to the hospital if you feel sick.
Don't refuse to see a doctor
because you don't wanna bother others.
I got it.
I also want to tell
you a few words.
Don't take things too seriously
but relax.
The more you worry,
the more troubles will arise.
Everything will be fine.
I remember.
♫ Stars in the sky ♫
♫ I pick some mushrooms. ♫
♫ Mushrooms can fill the basket. ♫
♫ I take out a pen. ♫
♫ The pen leaks ink. ♫
♫ What can I do? ♫
♫ I have piles of mung beans ♫
♫ Mung beans are delicious. ♫
♫ Gingers are tender. ♫
♫ Tender gingers taste pungent. ♫
♫ They pile up like a tower, ♫
♫ And the tower is tall. ♫
♫ With a slim figure. ♫
♫ My baby, let's go to sleep. ♫
♫ And the tower is tall. ♫
♫ With a slim figure. ♫
♫ My baby, let's go to sleep. ♫
♫ Stars in the sky ♫
♫ I pick some mushrooms. ♫
♫ Mushrooms can fill the basket. ♫
♫ I take out a pen. ♫
♫ The pen leaks ink. ♫
♫ What can I do? ♫
♫ I have piles of mung beans ♫
♫ Mung beans are delicious. ♫
♫ Gingers are tender. ♫
♫ Tender gingers taste pungent. ♫
♫ They pile up like a tower, ♫
♫ And the tower is tall. ♫
♫ With a slim figure. ♫
♫ My baby, let's go to sleep. ♫
♫ And the tower is tall. ♫
♫ With a slim figure. ♫
♫ My baby, let's go to sleep. ♫
Hello, Nana.
What's wrong?
Mr. Xie,
Hongdou had a fever
and got an IV drip this afternoon.
She hasn't come back yet.
Do you have time to pick her up?
I'll go right away.
♫ A feeling rushing out to me ♫
♫ spills my heart into the field ♫
♫ I know it. I will be yours. ♫
♫ Would you ask for any horse
but this one inside your heart? ♫
You...
You don't usually exercise, do you?
I don't exercise?
Why do you make me worried all day long?
Gosh.
What happened?
Why didn't you tell me that
you got a fever and needed to get an IV drip.
Just an IV drip.
Why should I tell you?
You shouldn't come alone.
I always went to the hospital alone
when I was in Beijing.
Are we in Beijing?
Weren't you angry with me this afternoon?
No matter I was angry or not,
I won't leave you alone like this.
It's not a serious disease.
I'm not that fragile.
I think you have lost your mind.
Look what time it is now.
When your IV is done,
it will be pitch dark outside.
Won't you be scared?
I've told Hu.
He'll come to pick me up
after he finished his work
in the downtown bar.
You really know
how to piss me off.
What's wrong with me?
How can I piss you off?
♫ I'll give you the saddle of my heart. ♫
Never mind.
You're sick.
I won't make a
fuss with a patient.
Cephalosporin?
The fever was caused by bacterial infection.
I need to get drips for three days.
My fever is gone.
Are you hungry?
No.
Well,
just sit down.
Don't stand in front
of me like a pillar.
I... I'm sorry
for this afternoon.
I didn't mean to do that.
Don't be angry.
Why did you apologize?
It's me who should apologize.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
But Wei is indeed
a pretty woman.
You should spend more time with her.
Perhaps you two can...
You know it.
She's a beauty.
Right?
What
is the smell?
The smell of disinfectant?
The smell of jealousy.
What's your problem?
Give me your hand.
Why?
Read your palm.
Screw you.
♫ A rainbow is ahead of the road. ♫
♫ We miss the chance to embrace each other. ♫
Are you cold?
♫ Where does true love hide? ♫
♫ Whose dream will it slip into? ♫
♫ In the street where the rain or sun falls, ♫
Here.
I added two eggs in it for you.
You don't have to eat all of the noodles,
but you need to eat the eggs.
This is too much.
I... I'll give you some.
It isn't that much.
You eat first.
Then leave it to me if you can't finish.
This is indeed too much.
Go get a bowl.
Okay then.
♫ Sometimes I find I fall in love. ♫
♫ Make a little wish and pray. ♫
♫ Maybe it will work out
the way you want it to. ♫
I'll help you eat some noodles.
You have to eat the eggs yourself.
I'll go get you a hot cup of tea.
What is
going on here?
What can happen between
a man and a woman?
Do you think
they're dating?
Damai said Everything
that happens now
will be flashbacks in the future.
Flashbacks?
You don't understand?
I'll go to write my songs.
Potato, potato.
I'm sweet potato.
(A funny code name to establish contact)
Stupid gag.
Hello, Xiaochun.
I'm at home.
She's here?
Okay, I'll go downstairs and pick her up.
Hongdou.
Miss, please go with her.
Okay.
Hello, how was your trip?
Good.
Xiaochun went to unload the goods.
She'll come over when she's done.
I'll show you to your room first.
Okay, thank you.
Luggage.
Give it to me.
The handle.
Okay.
I heard you had a fever
and got an IV drip yesterday.
I'm fine now. Thank you.
Then I should get going.
This way.
Thank you.
It's morning now so everyone
is busy with their work.
We'll give you a welcome party
this evening when everyone is back.
You don't have to.
It's fine.
This is the new tradition of the yard.
Your room is on the second floor.
Be careful. The stairs are a bit steep.
Is it too heavy for you?
Let me help you.
It's nothing.
It's not that heavy.
Watch your steps. The stairs are narrow.
The yard is quite large.
The yard is not
a public property.
It's combined by three independent houses.
Originally,
the place was rented out as an inn.
But it went out of business,
and has been idle for three years.
Later, Mr. Xie found a designer
to renovate the whole place again
and used it for short-term rentals.
There are six rooms here.
The public area is over there downstairs.
Let me show you the room.
Okay.
Here.
Your room was cleaned
up by the housekeeper
before you came.
Windows were opened for fresh air.
All the electrical appliances
have been checked
and there are no problems.
However,
she is only responsible for
the cleaning of public areas.
You may have to
clean the room yourself.
If you want the housekeeper
to clean it up for you,
you'll have to pay some extra money.
Got it.
By the way,
there is a big temperature difference
between morning and night,
and there are many mosquitoes at night.
I'll get you the pesticide later.
You can spray it in your room.
I have it in my room.
You don't need to buy it.
Thank you so much, Anytime.
Are you also the housekeeper here?
No, I'm not.
I'm the tenant next door.
I'm just doing a favor.
You're a tenant as well?
Yes.
If you don't say you're a tenant,
I thought
you'd been living here for a long time.
Why?
The vibe between you and the yard
seems harmonious.
I'm leaving in a couple of days.
But I'm still here these two days.
If you need anything, just ask me.
What a pity.
I just got here but you're leaving.
But our meeting here
is the result of serendipity.
You're right.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Bai Manjun.
You can call me Manjun.
Manjun.
Xu Hongdou.
Glad to meet you.
Glad to meet you, too.
Then you can unpack your luggage.
Xiaochun will come later.
She said she wanted to have lunch with you.
Okay.
Feel free to call me if you need anything.
Sure.
Thanks a lot.
It's nothing.
Xu Hongdolu.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
When do I need to get the IV drip?
Four o'clock.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Hongdou,
Why did you come back by yourself?
Where's Mr. Xie?
Xinxin just called.
She told him to go to the village committee
to mediate between the villagers.
Wait a moment.
It's you who went to pick up the new tenant.
Is she pretty?
How about this?
Since you know her,
you go upstairs and tell her to come down later.
I'll just sit here
and play the guitar with my back to her,
creating
a sense of mystique.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll go tell her.
Relax.
Don't be nervous.
How do I look?
Manjun,
are you free at the moment?
Let's go downstairs and take a break.
Sure.
Are you done tidying up your luggage?
Yes.
I don't have many stuffs.
You go downstairs first.
I'll go change my clothes.
Okay.
She's coming, Hu.
Get ready!
♫ The afternoon breeze is sweet, ♫
♫ blowing into a new season. ♫
♫ Your beautiful smile ♫
♫ is so pure and innocent. ♫
♫ Sometimes you're in a bad mood, ♫
♫ and I'm your comfort. ♫
♫ I wish happiness can always be with you. ♫
It is still the same song.
You are?
Sir,
a double expresso, please.
Thank you.
♫ Meeting you is like a bamboo forest
meeting early summer ♫
♫ and birds meeting the waves. ♫
♫ With you,
I'll never get lost in my adventure. ♫
♫ With you, I'll never
get lost in my adventure. ♫
♫ With you,
I'll never get lost in my adventure. ♫
Go away!
I'll just say a few words and then I'll go.
Miss,
whatever it is, it's gonna pass.
If you are having a hard time now,
you should
put the trouble aside for the moment.
You will find that what's
bothering you right now
will disappear itself
in the near future.
Even if you're obsessed with it,
it will finally... Thank you.
Be bygones.
That's all. Bye.
Mom.
What's wrong?
I'm in Beijing.
It's a music festival,
not a bar.
Music festival. Listen.
Sir,
get me another cup, please.
Okay.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
This is my coffee.
You!
Your cup.
I'll buy you a drink.
No. It's too late.
I won't drink.
It's so late now.
Why do you drink
double espresso.
Come on.
Come talk with me.
Alright.
Although we don't know each other,
since you're in a bad mood,
just see me as a shoulder to cry on.
Whatever you wanna say,
just talk to me.
I'm okay. I can stand it.
Let me show you something.
Where's my bag?
Divorce Certificate
of the People's Republic of China.
I've never even seen a marriage certificate yet,
but now I see a divorce certificate.
Don't they look the
same as each other?
Almost.
Seeing you like this...
Did your husband,
you ex-husband cheated on you?
No.
Then you cheated on him?
I didn't have the time.
I need to take care of my family,
my daughter, my ex-husband,
and my mother-in-law.
So you lived with your mother-in-law?
You didn't get along well with her?
No.
My mother-in-law lives upstairs.
She's very nice.
I actually married my ex-husband
because I thought my
mother-in-law was good.
Then
it's your ex who didn't treat you well.
Then you should divorce.
Not exactly.
My mom and dad can't
pick anything wrong with him.
Then why?
Since they're all nice,
why did you divorce?
I don't get it.
You don't need to understand.
Cheers.
I mean... lady,
you shouldn't drink too much.
Stop drinking.
Cheers.
Well,
now that you divorced,
you need to believe
that you will have a
happy and bright future.
Thank you.
♫ I always aspire to be closer to the ideal. ♫
♫ The more I long for it,
the more disoriented I become. ♫
♫ You're in a mess, and I'm flurried. ♫
♫ It is seeing everything,
but it doesn't tell anyone. ♫
♫ Some stop, some wander as always. ♫
♫ If life is a house,
then the days we spend in it are windows. ♫
♫ The stories we want
are happening right next to us. ♫
I saw her in a bad mood,
so I went up to persuade her
from the force of habit.
Thank you for not
treating me as a hooligan.
Hu seems to be a little roguish,
but in fact,
he is quite warm-hearted.
I agree. He told me that if
I feel bad and want to relax
for a while, I can come here
because the people here are very nice.
Yes. The people here are very nice.
But I didn't expect that
you could really come.
Right?
You didn't even leave
me your phone number.
I can search for this place online myself.
Pity.
You should tell Xiaochun
that you are my friend
and I invited you to come here
so that she can give you a discount on the rent.
Really?
Hu, you didn't get a discount
on your own rent either, did you?
You must have been an
excavator in a past life.
All you know is sabotage.
Manjun, eat some fruit.
Thanks.
Say that again!
You stole my corns.
Shame on you!
Those belong to me!
Don't fight!
Don't fight here!
Stop!
Stop fighting!
Mister!
What happened to you?
The villagers were having a fight.
I didn't have long hair for them to pull,
so they ripped my clothes.
You're scratched.
Where?
On your neck.
You could get an infection.
Come upstairs.
Let me cleanse your wound with iodine.
Then put it down.
What?
Put your hair down
so that I can climb up.
Spin your own thread.
Come in.
Are you packing?
Wait a second.
I'm looking for iodine.
Found it.
Wait.
Let me check.
His nails are really sharp.
If he scratched your face,
you'll be disfigured.
You didn't see his nails in person.
They've all turned brown because of smoking.
And It's all black under the nails.
Just cleanse the wound.
Don't breathe on my neck.
Sorry.
I did that subconsciously.
It's fine.
Keep going.
Keep going,
♫ I've been alone into the unknown. ♫
♫ Can navigate through the dark. ♫
Be careful when you
go back and shower.
Don't get water on the wound.
♫ A meadow of mine ♫
Then I should get going.
♫ A feeling rushing out to me ♫
By the way,
don't stay up too late.
Go to bed early.
You too,
Get some rest early.
♫ I'll give you the saddle of my heart. ♫
♫ I've been alone into the unknown. ♫
♫ Can navigate through the dark. ♫
♫ I'm searching for a meadow of mine ♫
♫ till you came in with the breeze. ♫
♫ A feeling rushing out to me
spills my heart into the field ♫
♫ I know it. I will be yours. ♫
♫ Would you ask for any horse
but this one inside your heart? ♫
♫ I'll give you the saddle of my heart. ♫
♫ A feeling rushing out to me
spills my heart into the field ♫
♫ I know it. I will be yours. ♫
♫ Would you ask for any horse
but this one inside your heart? ♫
♫ I'll give you the saddle of... ♫
♫ You asked me whether wind could sing. ♫
♫ We close our eyes to feel and smile. ♫
[A person you love (just let it be)
A life you want?]
♫ Listen to the rain
falling into the silent forest ♫
♫ Enjoy the mountainous landscape at sunset ♫
♫ The raindrops on the roof
fall into the eyes secretly ♫
♫ The world is like a quiet island ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ The sky is turning bright silently ♫
♫ Waiting for the seabirds
to call forth the ripples ♫
♫ Waiting for the sunlight to shine into
my heart across the lake ♫
♫ Set sail when it's windy ♫
♫ The reflection of clouds, the changing moon
and the stars all over the sky ♫
♫ The lost footsteps will be gradually erased ♫
♫ The light and shadow of four seasons ♫
♫ I've seen the meteor
that lights up the night sky ♫
♫ When the wind rises,
the sky will be cloudless ♫
♫ Go to a windy place to meet you ♫